<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ray Schneider</title>
    <link>https://rayschneider.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ray Schneider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:29:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rayschneider.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Readable AND Raidable</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/readablerandraidable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:29:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/readablerandraidable/</guid>
      <description>When I was younger, I won a competitive internship at one of our National Labs. At the time I was studying Earth Systems Science. I was assigned to the Underground Storage Technology department and given a mentor while I was there. I met a lot of interesting people. One of my favorite people I met there was not initially my mentor, but stepped into that role later. This is where I learned about &amp;lsquo;readable and raidable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Less Is More in ALL Things</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lessismore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:10:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lessismore/</guid>
      <description>Less Is More started for me as a joke many shared about the two pagers available on most if not all Linux and BSD based systems. The less pager had more features than the more pager.
Thats funny don&amp;rsquo;t you think? I know I do.
In any case, from that joke, and being a bit of a minimalist, I started applying it as a an operating concept for myself. Less is More in ALL Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Core Values</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/mycorevalues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:13:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/mycorevalues/</guid>
      <description>For at least the last 12 years or more, I have shared the following Core Values with teams and places I have worked. Now to be quite honest, I do not recall any longer if I built these on top of something else, or if I just generated these out of thin air from my own thoughts. So any semblance to others is a happy accident of like mindedness. I’m quite sure over the years, I have modified the wording a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working With Me</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/workingwithme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:06:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/workingwithme/</guid>
      <description>Working With Me
NOTE: I may update this in the future. Its not a static document.
Inspired by others I have seen over the years, I can&amp;rsquo;t claim complete originality for this sort of idea. I most definitely appreciate what it attempts to empower for anyone that is trying to work with the author of such a document.
Anyway, the following is intended to be a guide for working with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:01:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/about/</guid>
      <description>A Brief Professional Bio
Ray&amp;rsquo;s experience ranges from the seed funded startup to the Fortune 500 inside telecoms, ISP&amp;rsquo;s financials, media and security companies. Ray is a technical leader and problem solver, technically focused and solutions oriented team builder. He is known for delivery and has a reputation of getting things done. His background includes time spent from all vantage points of the software development lifecycle (SDLC). He has worked in: software and product development, systems programming, technical operations, automation, modern virtualization and containerization platforms, various cloud providers in on-prem, hybrid, and public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
