<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rmschneider</title>
    <link>https://rmschneider.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on rmschneider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 19:44:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rmschneider.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>End of 2019</title>
      <link>https://rmschneider.net/posts/endof2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 19:44:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmschneider.net/posts/endof2019/</guid>
      <description>Not a great year in my book. 2019 brought the passing of my father and my only living grandmother. My Dad before his time, and well, my grandmother, she was 96. Wow!
I&amp;rsquo;m ready for a New Year. I&amp;rsquo;m ready for 2019 to be behind me. I&amp;rsquo;m ready for 2020 and to get hammering on all sorts of projects. Rides, Runs, Mountains, Art, Botany, Work. Its the beginning of a new decade of life for me here at the tail end of the year as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://rmschneider.net/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 18:41:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmschneider.net/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Trying another hugo static site generation template. Maybe I will actually do some blogging this time around. Who knows.
I never seem to find the time though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Bio</title>
      <link>https://rmschneider.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 14:40:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmschneider.net/about/</guid>
      <description>A technically focused, solutions oriented team builder, who is known for delivery and has a reputation of getting things done, Ray has a strong career history leading in the areas of: software development, technical operations, automation, cloud and security to name a few. Ray has operated successfully in everything from a seed funded startup to Fortune 500 telecoms, ISP&amp;rsquo;s, financial, media and security companies.
Ray has mentored numerous people throughout his career that have gone on to attain the highest position levels of their careers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>