<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ray Schneider</title>
    <link>https://rayschneider.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ray Schneider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:13:16 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rayschneider.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Team Core Values</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/mycorevalues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:13:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/mycorevalues/</guid>
      <description>For at least the last 12 years or more, I have shared the following Core Values with teams and places I have worked. Now to be quite honest, I do not recall any longer if I built these on top of something else, or if I just generated these out of thin air from my own thoughts. So any semblance to others is a happy accident of like mindedness. I’m quite sure over the years, I have modified the wording a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working With Me</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/workingwithme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:06:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/workingwithme/</guid>
      <description>Working With Me
NOTE: I may update this in the future. Its not a static document.
Inspired by others I have seen over the years, I can&amp;rsquo;t claim complete originality for this document. I have seen others do this and thought it was a good idea. I have been meaning to do it for a while now, and finally got around to it. I hope you find it useful. I know I will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:01:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Ray&amp;rsquo;s experience ranges from seed funded startup to the Fortune 50 inside telecoms, ISP&amp;rsquo;s, financials, media and security companies. Ray is a technical leader, problem solver, and solutions oriented team builder. He is known for on-time, on-spec delivery with a reputation of getting things done. Ray&amp;rsquo;s background includes experience from all vantage points of the software and product lifecycle delivering some 30+ products with both internal and external customers so far.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
