<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ray Schneider</title>
    <link>https://rmschneider.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ray Schneider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:33:43 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rmschneider.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Core Values</title>
      <link>https://rmschneider.net/posts/corevalues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:33:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmschneider.net/posts/corevalues/</guid>
      <description>For at least the last 12 years or more, I have shared the following Core Values with teams and places I have worked. Now to be quite honest, I do not recall any longer if I built these on top of something else, or if I just generated these out of thin air from my own thoughts. So any semblance to others is a happy accident of like mindedness. I’m quite sure over the years, I have modified the wording a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://rmschneider.net/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:02:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmschneider.net/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>First Post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rmschneider.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:01:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmschneider.net/about/</guid>
      <description>A Brief Professional Bio
Ray&amp;rsquo;s experience ranges from the seed funded startup to the Fortune 500 inside telecoms, ISP&amp;rsquo;s financials, media and security companies. Ray is a technical leader and problem solver, technically focused and solutions oriented team builder. He is known for delivery and has a reputation of getting things done. His background includes time spent from all vantage points of the software development lifecycle (SDLC). He has worked in: software and product development, systems programming, technical operations, automation, modern virtualization and containerization platforms, various cloud providers in on-prem, hybrid, and public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
