<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ray Schneider</title>
    <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ray Schneider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:01:01 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rayschneider.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lock-In Is A State Of Mind</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lockin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:01:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lockin/</guid>
      <description>Lock-In&amp;hellip; Its heard all the time in technical circles. Its a bad thing. Its an undesirable situation. Avoiding lock-in is sometimes a full-time job. Recognizing the potential for lock-in is something that gets called out in meetings often. Lock-In is a concern without an option. Everything is lock-in. The truth is lock-in is just technical debt. It is technical debt that may or may not ever be realized. If it is realized, there is a definite cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome 2023</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/welcome2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 14:24:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/welcome2023/</guid>
      <description>Its already Feb! Its time to get myself in gear on this and start delivering. I put a stub in last year for projects. I never got to them. This year I intend to do just that. The projects will likely start off small, and largely be posted there as a way for myself to keep some notes about what I am doing and why I am doing it and how I did it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Learning</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lifelonglearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 14:27:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lifelonglearning/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to write a post about lifelong learning repeatedly. I&amp;rsquo;m punting as every post I have started about it doesn&amp;rsquo;t measure up to what I would really like to say.
Lifelong Learning is a part of the experience.
I&amp;rsquo;m a lifelong learner. We all are, even if we do not recognize it yet. Some learn fast, some slow, some easy, some hard, some read, some do, some fake it, some act it, some listen for it, some have to speak it, other write, draw, paint, program, ride, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Very Interesting</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/veryinteresting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 17:47:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/veryinteresting/</guid>
      <description>I used to be that guy who was heard in every meeting. I was generally loud, or attempting to correct where I thought something was wrong. I would get complaints about being too aggressive, unapproachable, or intimidating. I once pissed off a senior technical person so badly he went straight to his leadership. I ended up in my own meeting and later was sent to a &amp;lsquo;communication course.&amp;rsquo; (Another side story, the instructor of that course said that based on what he had seen in the course, I had no need to take it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readable AND Raidable</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/readablerandraidable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:29:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/readablerandraidable/</guid>
      <description>When I was younger, I won a competitive internship at one of our National Labs. At the time I was studying Earth Systems Science. I was assigned to the Underground Storage Technology department and given a mentor while I was there. I met a lot of interesting people. One of my favorite people I met there was not initially my mentor, but stepped into that role later. This is where I learned about &amp;lsquo;readable and raidable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Less Is More in ALL Things</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lessismore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:10:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/lessismore/</guid>
      <description>Less Is More started for me as a joke many shared about the two pagers available on most if not all Linux and BSD based systems. The less pager had more features than the more pager.
Thats funny don&amp;rsquo;t you think? I know I do.
In any case, from that joke, and being a bit of a minimalist, I started applying it as a an operating concept for myself. Less is More in ALL Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Core Values</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/mycorevalues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:13:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/mycorevalues/</guid>
      <description>For at least the last 12 years or more, I have shared the following Core Values with teams and places I have worked. Now to be quite honest, I do not recall any longer if I built these on top of something else, or if I just generated these out of thin air from my own thoughts. So any semblance to others is a happy accident of like mindedness. I’m quite sure over the years, I have modified the wording a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working With Me</title>
      <link>https://rayschneider.net/posts/workingwithme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:06:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rayschneider.net/posts/workingwithme/</guid>
      <description>Working With Me
NOTE: I may update this in the future. Its not a static document.
Inspired by others I have seen over the years, I can&amp;rsquo;t claim complete originality for this sort of idea. I most definitely appreciate what it attempts to do for anyone that is trying to work with the author.
The following is intended to be a guide for working with me. It attempts to compile a group of areas and methods with an eye towards our collaboration in the workplace being efficient and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
